When I realized that I was there,
only one of them was there.
For money, I fell into the dungeon,
and my parents died.
For living...
just for living...
I fell.
There's not been in development.
Don't break it.
Take a step of practice!
You made a hit,
You know?
See that,
You're dead,
and you kept your arm by attacking me,
It was out there
It broke his place
I don't know how to do it.
Lili is a dreamer.
Lili is...
...and I don't know how to do it.
Oh, yeah!
It's a lot of fun, too!
It's a long time, though, yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Then, Kami, Loki, Soma Familyiaの構成員が崇めているのは
神ではなくそのお酒だと…
Oh, yeah!
You are right, right, right?
このクソ高い酒もあいつにとっては失敗作
あの連中が崇拝しとるのは
市場に出回らん完成品の酒や
完成品?
せや あれはヤバイで
一口飲むだけで心から酔いしれる
Soma Familyiaの子供たちはみんなあれを飲むためにあそこにおる
つながりは酒だけや
そんな… ただそれだけのファミリアだと言うんですか?
それだけや
酒作りに没頭するには金がいる
せやから稼ぎの多いやつには完成品をちびっと飲ませる
一度でも味わったやつはまた飲みたーなって必死に稼ぐ
市場リスでも多く
仲間を蹴落としてでも
他人を犠牲にしてでもな
あっ…
まあ うちの知ってるのはそんなとこや
役に立ったか エイナちゃん?
はい ありがとうございました
ほれ アイズたん
なんや 男に逃げられたからって いつまで落ち込んでんねや
セータス更新しよう
なっ なっ
分かりました
アッヒヒヒ ヤワハダ ジューリーしたるわ
変なことしたら 切りますよ
マジで?
おもしろい髪ですね
面白いかどうかはともかく
あれで損害に切れる
われわれからの信頼も厚い
ふん…
他人を犠牲にしてでもか
レベル4
え-っ?
I can't wait the
Oh
Well, I know you're a supporter now
Yes
Ms. Lily, don't worry, that's a 7SK's
Let's take it away
Bellくん
Ah, yes?
You're a person who honestly is listening to my defense.
Right now?
You can without father's talking.
I'll have to understand that she has a knife so that she could take seriously.
skrr?
As someone who you had Pony Jeffs worked on,
So I think she'sudo-
The king said it.
Oh, how do you go?
Yay, before we fulfill it.
Conradly make your talent go fine.
dasخبر、 but I think you'd be Trudyège who was wished
and it'dкой alike for me too.
It's been a tenha monster.
I've got a Problem today that you don't see yesterday!
It's the fact that you'd please show us the magic of mine.
You are here for the rest of your year.
My trainer will be on to see you.
Ha ha Mam…
Six weeks later
I felt like I had your relationship with the Phestily
But, if I wasabbel in the investigation, my wife
Well, I'd like to this side.
Let me support you with the Sopoctausla
Uh…
Liliの提案を聞いていただいて ありがとうございます
Liliはベル様のサポーターに慣れて 本当に幸運でした
うん まあ 10階層だって いずれは行かなきゃならないからね
それで…
ん?
差出がましいようなのですが ベル様
So we're here.
You can't use this enough.
C droid.
Litet my arm now.
It's very difficult to PHP to create your monster.
It's a bit impossible to reach it on top.
But...
Umm...
L Deixa my arm...
Mmm...
Ok...
Right!
Come on!
lilly.
Menotaulis?
Yes,
his name is Belgranell.
A,
An about the letter?
Are you scared of me?
What?
No!
I'm so grateful for you!
Really?
Good...
...
ここが10階層?
はい、今回の目的地です
はあ…
あっ…
危ないから離れないでね、リリー
はい、ビル様
リリー、これって…
はい、ランドフォームです
しかし、処理している暇はないようです
今はないようです
やっぱり大きい
逃げてはいけませんよ、ベル様
そうだよね
オークを倒せないようじゃ
この先のモンスターなんて一生攻略できない
そうだ、ミノタオロスだって
あっ…
ランドフォーム!
天然の武器庫!
ベル様、来ます!
どういうつもりだい、アドバイザー君
君はギルドの用事で来たんだろう
僕と話している暇があるのかい?
ご相談というのは
ベル君の例のサポーターについてです
彼女は危険だと思います
危険だと思います
よし…
ベル様、もう一匹来ます!
ファイヤーボルト!
勝てた…
やったよ、リリー
リリー、どこ?
まさか、モンスターに…
んっ…
これ…
モンスターを…
おびき寄せるための…
あっ…
リリー、どこなの?
ファイヤーボルト!
リリー!
どこ?
あ…
平時して!
ファイヤーボルト!
あ…
リリー?!
リリー!?
何してるの!?
ごめんなさい…
ベル様
もうここまでです
ファイヤーボルト!
You led me to proszę everything, right?
What? What did you do?
躍, try to step out now.
That's my friend, Perúng virtus.
Guys are bad enough, right?
The sound of the 12th of the song is the Shinder Era.
I'm not sure if I can meet you.
I don't know if I can meet you.
I'm a villain.
I'm a weapon.
I can't even buy this.
I can't even buy this money.
I'm a villain.
I need money.
That's why...
You're good.
You're a villain.
I'madeK richtig.
You're kör.
It's промenself.
He's laptines!
Gunnarsich!
Owl, men are you!
Good to see you!
You will learn to hear it.
Later, that guy I still got there.
I want to work with a lot.
What an interesting consequences.
You're about to stop the Ana!
You didn't cost me the new approach, not too.
You couldn't do all that.
It didn't 그때 what I've come to!
You don't take Cartman HOL.
Give me some.
You'll have a winner now.
Things are on Monday, not for hours.
You got him.
Oh, you know, man.
負けんまで持ってやがってよ
やっぱり お前らの言うとおり 髪込んでるみたいだぜ こいつ
そうですかい
ねぇ 旦那
ひとつお願いがあるんですが
そいつの持ち物 全部置いてってほしいんでさ
うっ
うっ…
キラート!
て…てめえ 何やってるかわかってんのか?
Aye.
The killer ant had me
SEE the message in the
That's...
Tomorrow.
You're the good people.
You're the country, right?
I'm a help숙iving, better than...
I almost get you through.
It's tough that you guys morning, too.
What about what do you do?
So...
You know whereabouts are you?
The rent was the Doris responsibility price,
coins I spent 하 as well.
It was too high to an revolt!
Uh…
Carl!
Look at you.
This great fight.
Look.
.
So...
The
Aaaaaaah!
This is because of the dream.
But it's true, isn't it?
This is...
...that...
...it...
Does this mean you can willingly...
...which will matter, you love...
...that?
Purely, and now...
...cries...
ப Mش辰 Cloud
...that...
...to die...
...what'sendi, and more sou,
...receptor...
...to die.
....
...but...
...severentissimo.
Yet, it's time building has been brought and destroyed
Since it could have been not done
We'veeded, we've been talworldous
We've never никed
We'vecalled all...
He's.
Is it going to stop?
Mission high!
Please, Kami, Hestia.
I can tell you what I'm saying, but...
I'm going to help you.
Yes?
Stop!
Youition so much!
I'm coming back to help you.
It's stress, Gen subscribers.
It actually looks like I already did the ghost.
Be sure to feel!
You're not alone!
...